BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series V: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
  - Code no.16: Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation and International Association of Machinists, Lodge 609, AFL-CIO, 1962-1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Code no.18: Olin Mathieson Chemical Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, District 9, 1968- 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Code no.20: Dow Chemical Company, Rocky Flats Plant and Denver Metal Trades Council, AFL-CIO, 1960-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Code no.21: Pomona Division of General Dynamics Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, District 120, Lodge 1233, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Code no.25: Northern Ordnance Division, FMC Corporation and International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1964-1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Code no.27: Olin Corporation, Energy Systems Division and International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oilers, Local 320, AFL-CIO, 1966- 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Code no.35: Sperry Rand Corporation and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 228, 1971- 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2500: Interlake Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Code no.2503: American Metal Products Company and International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, Local 174, 1958-1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Code no.2504: Armco Steel Corporation and Armco Employees Independent Federation, Inc., 1960-1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Code no.2505: Armco Steel Corporation and Butler Armco Employee Representatives, 1960-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Code no.2510: Bethlehem Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Code no.2511: A.M. Byers Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Code no.2514: Continental Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1054, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Code no.2516: Copperweld Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 2243, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Code no.2517: Crucible Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Code no.2518: Detroit Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1962-1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Code no.2520: Empire-Reeves Steel Division, Cyclops Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Code no.2521: Firth Sterling, Inc. and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Code no.2522: Granite City Steel Co. and United Steelworkers of America, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Code no.2523: Great Lakes Steel and United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Code no.2524: Inland Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, 1968-1971 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Code no.2525: Wisconsin Steel Works and Progressive Steel Workers Union, 1960-1968 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Code no.2526: Jones and Laughlin Steel Corporation and United Steelworkers of America, 1960-1971 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Code no.2529: Keystone Steel and Wire Company and Independent Steel Workers Alliance, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Code no.2530: Laclede Steel Company, Alton Works and United Steel Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Code no.2532: Lukens Steel Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Code no.2533: Midvale-Heppenstall Company and Federal Labor Union, Local No. 18887, 1959-1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Code no.2534: Weirton Steel Company and Independent Steelworkers Union, 1962-1971 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Code no.874: National Hand Embroidery and Novelty Manufacturers Association, Inc. and Bonnaz, Embroideries, Tucking, Pleating and Allied Crafts Union, Local 66, 1964-1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Code no.877: Irving Air Chute Co., Inc. and AFL-CIO United Textile Workers of America, Local 277, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Code no.1012: Picture Frame Manufacturing Companies and Upholsterers' International Union, AFL-CIO, 1959-1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Code no.1018: Picture and Mirror Frame Manufacturers Association, Inc. and Picture and Mirror Frames and Moulding Workers Union, Local 3127, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Code no.1103: Kroehler Mfg. Co. and Upholsterers' International Union, AFL-CIO, 1968-1971 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Code no.1104: Southern California Assn. of Cabinet Manufacturers and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1962- 1971 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Code no.1105: Upholstered Furniture Manufacturers' Association of California and Upholsterers' International Union, AFL-CIO, Locals 15 and 15A, 1959-1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Code no.1106: Upholstered Furniture Manufacturers' Association of the Metropolitan District, New York and Upholsterers' and Springmakers' Union, Local 76, AFL-CIO, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Code no.1108: General Fireproofing Company and United Steelworkers of America, Local 1617, 1960-1968 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Code no.1109: American Seating Company and United Automobile Workers of America, Local 135, 1961-1970 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Code no.1111: Store Fixture and Architectural Woodwork Institute and Cabinet Makers and Millmen United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Code no.1112: Eastern Products Corporation and United Furniture Workers of America, AFL-CIO, Local 75, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Code no.1113: Hamilton Manufacturing Company and United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners, Local 1533, AFL-CIO, 1960- 1970 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Code no.1115: Furniture Group Incorporated and Furniture Workers Union, Local 76B, 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Code no.1116: Simmons Company and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Code no.1118: Industrial Relations Council of Furniture Manufacturers in Southern California and Furniture Workers Union, Local 3161, AFL-CIO, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Code no.1119: Chicago Furniture Manufacturer's Association and the Upholsterer's International Union of North America, Local 18, AFL-CIO, 1964-1967 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Code no.1120: Williams Furniture Corporation and United Furniture Workers of America, Local 273, 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Code no.1121: Curtis Mathes Manufacturing Company and United Furniture Workers of America, Locals 376.377, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Code no.1122: All-Steel Equipment, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Code no.1124: Schnadig Corporation and Upholsterers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Code no.1131: Manufacturing Woodworkers Association of Greater New York, Inc. and District Council of New York City and Vicinity of the United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America, 1961-1967 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Series VI: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
  - Code no.286: Wholesale Bread Shops, Wholesale Cake Bakeries and Retail Bakeries and Bakery and Confectionery Workers International Union of America, Local 3, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Code no.290: Wholesale Bakers' Group and Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America, Locals 31 and 37, 1967- 1970 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Code no.226: Associated Milk Dealers, Inc. and Milk Drivers' Union, Local 753, International Brotherhood of Teamsters, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Code no.227: Associated Milk Dealers of Denver, Inc. and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 537, 1968-1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Code no.238: St. Louis, Missouri, Milk and Ice Cream Employers and Milk and Ice Cream Drivers, Dairy Employees and Allied Food Industries Union, Local 603, 1967-1973 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Code no.240: Milk Industry and Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Local 584, 1969-1973 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Series VII: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.285: Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Salesclerks Union, Local 150, 1959-1959 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Salesclerks Union, Local 150, 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Agreement effective 2/1/1956 and expires on 1/31/1959. Covers an unknown number of workers in Georgia, Alabama, Tennessee
      Format: Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA).
    - Item 2: Specialty Bakery Owners of America, Inc. and Bakery and Confectionery Salesclerks Union, Local 150, 1956-1959; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Series VIII: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
  - Code no.3320: Page Aircraft Maintenance, Inc. and International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Locals 2003,2262, 1969- 1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Series IX: Industry Code #51, Information
  - Code no.1441: Pulitzer Publishing Company and St. Louis Newspaper Guild, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Code no.1442: World Journal Tribune and Newspaper Guild of New York, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Code no.1444: Curtis Publishing Company and Curtis Council of Unions, 1967-1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)